# Ruo-Fang Wang (Karen Wang)

4-year work experience in Marketing and learning background from Economic to Web development & UIUX.

wango857@algonquinlive.com | +1-343-777-6893

1385 Woodroffe Avenue, Ottawa, ON K2G 1V8

I originally graduated from the Department of Economics at National Taipei University in Taiwanand had marketing work experiences in a foreign company and design experience in a non-profitorganization. Currently, I am learning web development and UI/UX in the Interactive Media Designprogram at Algonquin College. I'm good at learning new things and team-working and can multitaskafter getting familiar with my job.

## Education

#### **Diploma in Interactive Media Design**

Algonquin College - Ottawa, ON, Canada Level 1: Dean's Honours; GPA 4.0 / 4.0 September 2021 to Present

### **Bachelor's Degree in Economics**

National Taipei University - Taipei, Taiwan

GPA: Overall 3.48/4.0

September 2013 to June 2017

## **Program-Related Skills**

Web Development Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, PHP

Design and Photogrphy Processing Tools:

Adobe: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Lightroom

Software Tools:

Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Teams

**Web Analysis Tools:** Adobe Analytics **UX and Web Design Tools:** Adobe XD

- Research for Targeting Audience and create Personas.
- Based on Personas to design the user flow and website in Adobe XD.
- Create high-fidelity prototypes in Adobe XD for further web development.
- Develop interactive websites with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, and Bootstrap.

#### Additional Qualifications

- Well time management: Deal with multiple projects simultaneously and launch them on schedule.
- Team Working: Ability to work for projects in various project-based teams.
- Problem-solving: Independently think and investigate problems, and come up with solutions after clarification with counterparts.
- Stress Resistance: Ability to work well under pressure.

# Ruo-Fang Wang (Karen Wang)

4-year work experience in Marketing and learning background from Economic to Web development & UIUX.

wango857@algonquinlive.com | +1-343-777-6893

1385 Woodroffe Avenue, Ottawa, ON K2G 1V8

## **Related Experience**

#### **Academic Projects**

Re-design websites for Sushi Kan to improve its user experience of online order:

- Research for its Targeting Audience and create Personas.
- Based on the TA and Personas to design the user flow and websites in Adobe XD.
- Create low-fidelity and high-fidelity prototypes in Adobe XD.
- Develop interactive websites with HTML, CSS, and jQuery.

# Other Work Experience

#### Marketing Officer - DBS Bank (Taiwan) - Taipei, Taiwan

July 2018 to April 2021

- Planned Marketing Strategy for bunches of Consumers bank products from branch communication to digital marketing. Maintained CPL as CAD 27 in digital marketing of mortgage loans.
- Planned Social Media for Consumers bank products, such as loans, deposits, and investment products.
- Leveraged the resources from DBS Bank (Singapore) to create 21 articles and videos. Launched the bi-weekly and daily newsletters of investment products for our wealth clients to increase the awareness of our investment branding within our wealth clients' coverage.
- Planned and held webinars for unit funds, achieving the product goal within one month.

#### Marketing Specialist (Contract) - Citi Bank (Taiwan) - Taipei, Taiwan

June 2017 to June 2018

- Responsible for Social Media and Digital Marketing materials for credit cards and personal loans.
- Managed Digital Marketing materials to ensure the information was concurred by Legal and Compliance.
- Executed A/B testing for digital marketing banners. Found our more appealing design to gain more leads. For example, we tested out that the design of one card face plus a best-offer wording was the best to acquire credit card leads.

#### Marketing Assistant (Internship) - Microsoft (Taiwan) - Taipei, Taiwan

June 2016 to June 2017

Served as a one-year intern in the Small and Medium Business (SMB) Sales Department. My works included:

- Generated daily sales reports.
- Maintained customer service emails.
- Leveraged the resources of the Microsoft group to design banners for webinars and other marketing campaign materials.
- Served as a front desk hosting for any physical seminar/activities for our SMB clients.

# **Ruo-Fang Wang (Karen Wang)**

4-year work experience in Marketing and learning background from Economic to Web development & UIUX.

wango857@algonquinlive.com | +1-343-777-6893

1385 Woodroffe Avenue, Ottawa, ON K2G 1V8

# Other Work Experience

#### Marketing Intern

July 2014 to August 2014

Taiwan Women's Development Association (A non-profit organization) - Taipei, Taiwan

- Used Photoshop to design DM, cards, catalog, and LOGO of Tamsui Fish shop to promote those handicrafts made by single mothers in Tamsui Fish shop.
- Won the North District Champion in a wrap-up presentation competition of Youth Development Administration, Ministry of Education in Taiwan.

### **Volunteer and Co-curricular Activities**

### NTPU Zither Club President - National Taipei University, Taipei, Taiwan

July 2015 to June 2016

- Recruited more club members from 8 to more than 20 members.
- Planned and led club members to hold many activities to amplify the awareness of Zither Club, such as Campus Stall Activity and Anniversary Music Concert.

### References

#### **Charles Watson**

CBG Marketing Head
DBS Bank (Taiwan)

Email: charlesooo@dbsbank.com

Phone: +1-234-5678

#### Kayla Bledel

Web Development Professor Algonquin College

Email: kaylaooo@algonquincollege.com

Phone: +1-567-8901